A Guide to the National Committee on United States-China Relations records, RG 1, Accession 1 FA772
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Exchanges from China, 4
  - ACJA Law Journalists Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 1998 October 16-30 (Box 98, Folder 1458)
    New York, Philadelphia, Washington, DC, Los Angeles, and Honolulu. Visit sponsored by the All-China Journalists Association (ACJA).
  - ACJA Law Journalists Delegation - Travel Arrangements, 1998 October (Box 99, Folder 1459)
    Transportation and Hotels. Visit sponsored by the All-China Journalists Association (ACJA).
  - ACJA Law Journalists Delegation - Reports, Itinerary, Brochure, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1998 October 16-30 (Box 99, Folder 1460)
    File includes Namelists and Bios. Visit sponsored by the All-China Journalists Association (ACJA).
  - ACJA Law Journalists Delegation - Reports, Itinerary, Brochure, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1998 October 16-30; FA772:057; Still Image (Box 147, Folder 1460)
    Delegates at dinner hosted by Paul Gewirtz and Zoe Baird.
  - Institute of World Development, 1998 October 19-22 (Box 99, Folder 1461)
  - Hu Angang and Ni Jianmin Visit, 1998 October 21-22 (Box 99, Folder 1462)
    Professors Hu and Ni were affiliated with the Association of Chinese Political Studies
  - Law School Deans Delegation - Brochure, Namelists, Bios, Background, and Planning, 1998 October 30-November 13 (Box 99, Folder 1463)
  - Law School Deans Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 1998 October 30-November 13 (Box 99, Folder 1464)
    San Francisco (Berkeley and Stanford), Ann Arbor, Boston, Washington, DC, New York, and New Haven.
  - Law School Deans Delegation - Follow-Ups (Box 99, Folder 1465)
  - Environmental Education NGO Leadership Delegation - Background and Planning, 1998 November 28-December 11 (Box 99, Folder 1466)
    Delegation from Hong Kong, Taiwan, and Beijing.
  - Environmental Education NGO Leadership Delegation - Prior Planning and Background, 1998 November 28-December 11 (Box 99, Folder 1467)
    Original folder labeled "Background - Old." Includes correspondence from 1997. Delegation from Hong Kong, Taiwan, and Beijing.
  - Environmental Education NGO Leadership Delegation - Namelist, Itinerary, Brochure, 1998 November 28-December 11 (Box 100, Folder 1468)
  - Environmental Education NGO Leadership Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 1998 November 28-December 11 (Box 100, Folder 1469)
    Louisiana, Austin, TX, and San Francisco. Delegation from Hong Kong, Taiwan, and Beijing.
  - Environmental Education NGO Leadership Delegation - Report, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1998 November 28-December 11 (Box 100, Folder 1470)
  - Foreign Policy Journal Editors Delegation - Background Information and Research, 1999 January 23-February 6 (Box 100, Folder 1471)
  - Foreign Policy Journal Editors Delegation - Chinese People's Institute of Foreign Affairs (CPIFA) Correspondence, 1999 January 23-February 6 (Box 100, Folder 1472)
  - Foreign Policy Journal Editors Delegation - Program and Scheduling Correspondence, 1999 January 23-February 6 (Box 100, Folder 1473)
  - Foreign Policy Journal Editors Delegation - Report, Itinerary, Namelist, and Brochure, 1999 January 23-February 6 (Box 100, Folder 1474)
  - Foreign Policy Journal Editors Delegation - Report, Itinerary, Namelist, and Brochure, 1999 January 23-February 6; FA772:058; Still Image (Box 147, Folder 1474)
    Group photo of delegation on Columbia University campus.
  - Foreign Policy Journal Editors Delegation - Thank Yous and Follow-Up, 1999 January 23-February 6 (Box 100, Folder 1475)
  - Foreign Policy Journal Editors Delegation - Thank Yous and Follow-Up, 1999 January 23-February 6; FA772:059; Still Image (Box 147, Folder 1475)
    27 snapshots (and negatives) of delegation's trip
  - Social Safety Net Delegation - Itinerary, Namelist, Brochure, Background, and Planning, 1999 April 24-May 8 (Box 100, Folder 1476)
  - Social Safety Net Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 1999 April 24-May 8 (Box 100, Folder 1477)
    New York, Washington, DC, and Michigan (Lansing and Detroit).
  - Social Safety Net Delegation - Thank Yous and Follow-Up, 1999 April 24-May 8 (Box 100, Folder 1478)
  - Teacher Education and Training Delegation - Background and Planning, 1999 June 5-19 (Box 100, Folder 1479)
  - Teacher Education and Training Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 1999 June 5-19 (Box 101, Folder 1480)
    New York, Washington, DC, Atlanta, and San Francisco.
  - Teacher Education and Training Delegation - Report, Itinerary, Namelist, Brochure, and Follow-Up, 1999 June 5-19 (Box 101, Folder 1481)
  - Teacher Education and Training Delegation - Report, Itinerary, Namelist, Brochure, and Follow-Up, 1999 June 5-19; FA772:182; Still image (Box 147, Folder 1481)
    10 snapshots of delegation trip.
  - Television Broadcast Delegation - Background, Namelist, and Itinerary, 1999 June (Box 101, Folder 1482)
    File includes presentations from the 1998 trip to China.
  - Television Broadcast Delegation - Correspondence with China, 1999 June 12-26 (Box 101, Folder 1483)
  - Television Broadcast Delegation - Planning (New York), 1999 June 12-26 (Box 101, Folder 1484)
  - Television Broadcast Delegation - Planning (Washington, DC), 1999 June 12-26 (Box 101, Folder 1485)
  - Television Broadcast Delegation - Planning (Nashville), 1999 June 12-26 (Box 101, Folder 1486)
  - Television Broadcast Delegation - Planning (Nashville), 1999 June 12-26; FA772:060; Still Image (Box 147, Folder 1486)
    Delegation at the Wild Horse Saloon.
  - Television Broadcast Delegation - Planning (Los Angeles), 1999 June 12-26 (Box 101, Folder 1487)
  - Television Broadcast Delegation - Report, Brochure, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1999 June 12-26 (Box 101, Folder 1488)
  - Television Broadcast Delegation - Report, Brochure, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1999 June 12-26; FA772:061; Still Image (Box 147, Folder 1488)
    Snapshots (and negatives) of delegation trip and group photos.
  - Taiwan Local Energy/Transportation Leadership Delegation - Brochure, Namelist, Background, and Planning, 1999 September 11-23 (Box 101, Folder 1489)
    Includes some materials in Chinese.
  - Taiwan Local Energy/Transportation Leadership Delegation - Participants, 1999 September 11-23 (Box 101, Folder 1490)
    Accepted delegates and Other Nominees.
  - Taiwan Local Energy/Transportation Leadership Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 1999 September 11-23 (Box 101, Folder 1491)
    Los Angeles, Santa Barbara, San Diego, Portland, and Seattle.
  - Taiwan Local Energy/Transportation Leadership Delegation - Report, Itinerary, Thank Yous, and Follow Up, 1999 September 11-23 (Box 101, Folder 1492)
  - Secondary Education Delegation - General, 1999 October 16-30 (Box 102, Folder 1493)
    Includes Brochure, Namelist, Itinerary, Report, Background, Planning, and Follow-Up.
  - Secondary Education Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 1999 October 16-30 (Box 102, Folder 1494)
    Denver, New York, and San Francisco
  - Secondary Education Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 1999 October 16-30; FA772:062; Still Image (Box 147, Folder 1494)
    Denver, New York, and San Francisco. Snapshots of delegation in Denver and San Francisco.
  - Municipal Legislative Modernization Delegation - General, 1999 October 22 -November 5 (Box 102, Folder 1495)
    Includes Brochure, Namelist, Background and Planning, and Correspondence with the Chinese People's Institute of Foreign Affairs.
  - Municipal Legislative Modernization Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 1999 October 22 -November 5 (Box 102, Folder 1496)
    Washington, DC, Detroit, and San Francisco.
  - Municipal Legislative Modernization Delegation - Reports and Itinerary, 1999 October 22 -November 5 (Box 102, Folder 1497)
  - Municipal Legislative Modernization Delegation - Reports and Itinerary, 1999 October 22 -November 5; FA772:063; Still Image (Box 147, Folder 1497)
    Group photo and 2 snapshots, with identifications. Negatives (multiple strips)
  - Local Environment Protection Leaders Delegation, 1999 November 6-19 (Box 102, Folder 1498)
    Visit sponsored by the Luce Foundation and the United States Information Agency, in connection with the NCUSCR's Civil Society project.
  - Tibet Vocational Education Delegation - Background and Planning, 2000 March 4-18 (Box 102, Folder 1499)
    Includes Interpreter arrangements.
  - Tibet Vocational Education Delegation - Brochure, Namelist, Bios, and Itinerary, 2000 March 4-18 (Box 102, Folder 1500)
  - Tibet Vocational Education Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 2000 March 4-18 (Box 102, Folder 1501)
    Boston, Illinois, New Mexico, Arizona, and San Francisco. Includes travel and hotel arrangements.
  - Tibet Vocational Education Delegation - Reports, Itinerary, and Follow-Up, 2000 March 4-18 (Box 102, Folder 1502)
  - Minority Education Delegation - Background, Planning, Namelists, and Brochure, 2000 May 5-19 (Box 102, Folder 1503)
    Includes unidentified document in Chinese.
  - Minority Education Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 2000 May 5-19 (Box 102, Folder 1504)
    Washington, DC, San Antonio, Albuequerque, Santa Fe, and San Francisco.
  - Minority Education Delegation - Visits and Meetings (Literature), 2000 May 5-19 (Box 102, Folder 1505)
  - Minority Education Delegation - Visits and Meetings (Literature), 2000 May 5-19 (Box 103, Folder 1506)
  - Minority Education Delegation - Visits and Meetings (Literature), 2000 May 5-19 (Box 103, Folder 1507)
  - Minority Education Delegation - Report, Itinerary, and Follow-Up, 2000 May 5-19 (Box 103, Folder 1508)
  - Minority Education Delegation - Report, Itinerary, and Follow-Up, 2000 May 5-19; FA772:064; Still Image (Box 147, Folder 1508)
    Snapshot of 3 delegates by Golden Gate Bridge.
  - Guizhou Private Vocational Education Study Tour - Brochure, Itinerary, Planning, 2000 May 16-30 (Box 103, Folder 1509)
    The Luce Foundation helped sponsor the visit of this delegation from Guizhou province.
  - Guizhou Private Vocational Education Study Tour - Correspondence with Chinese, 2000 May 16-30 (Box 103, Folder 1510)
  - Guizhou Private Vocational Education Study Tour - New York, 2000 May 16-30 (Box 103, Folder 1511)
    New York, Washington, DC, Kentucky, Illinois, and San Francisco.
  - Guizhou Private Vocational Education Study Tour - Thank Yous and Follow-Up, 2000 May 16-30 (Box 103, Folder 1512)
  - Educational Evaluation Delegation - Background and Planning, 2000 September 23-October 7 (Box 103, Folder 1513)
  - Educational Evaluation Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 2000 September 23-October 7 (Box 103, Folder 1514)
    New York, Washington, DC, Colorado, and San Francisco. Includes hotel and travel arrangements.
  - Educational Evaluation Delegation - Report, Itinerary, Namelist, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 2000 September 23-October 7 (Box 103, Folder 1515)
  - Anhui Delegation, 2000 September 26 (Box 103, Folder 1516)
    The NCUSCR helped with arrangements for this delegation from Anhui province's one-day visit to New York.
  - Civil Trial Procedure Delegation of Shanghai and Jinan Judges - Background, Brochure, Namelists, and Itinerary, 2000 October 20-November 4 (Box 103, Folder 1517)
  - Civil Trial Procedure Delegation of Shanghai and Jinan Judges - Correspondence with China, 2000 October 20-November 4 (Box 103, Folder 1518)
  - Civil Trial Procedure Delegation of Shanghai and Jinan Judges - Visits and Meetings, 2000 October 20-November 4 (Box 104, Folder 1519)
    Washington, DC, Boston, Chicago, San Francisco, and Los Angeles.
  - Civil Trial Procedure Delegation of Shanghai and Jinan Judges - Visits and Meetings, 2000 October 20-November 4; FA772:065; Still Image (Box 147, Folder 1519)
    Photos of delegates in meetings and on trip. Also includes set of negatives.
  - Civil Trial Procedure Delegation of Shanghai and Jinan Judges - Follow Up, 2000 October 20-November 4 (Box 104, Folder 1520)
  - Supreme People's Court Delegation - Background (Proposed 1999 Visit), 2001 February 9-23 (Box 104, Folder 1521)
    Budgeting and planning for a Senior Judicial Delegation visit proposed for November 1999.
  - Supreme People's Court Delegation - Brochure, Bios, Background, and Planning, 2001 February 9-23 (Box 104, Folder 1522)
  - Supreme People's Court Delegation - Brochure, Bios, Background, and Planning, 2001 February 9-23; FA772:066; Still Image (Box 147, Folder 1522)
    Group photo of delegates.
  - Supreme People's Court Delegation - Correspondence with China, 2001 February 9-23 (Box 104, Folder 1523)
  - Supreme People's Court Delegation - Ford Foundation, 2001 February 9-23 (Box 104, Folder 1524)
  - Supreme People's Court Delegation - Translation, 2001 February 9-23 (Box 104, Folder 1525)
    File includes two papers on Judicial Independence, in English and Chinese.
  - Supreme People's Court Delegation - Translation, 2001 February 9-23; Digital: 3.5-inch floppy disk (Box 104, Folder 1525)
    Disk labeled "National Committee Transparencies, Transparencies 2.
  - Supreme People's Court Delegation - Translation, 2001 February 9-23; Digital: 3.5-inch floppy disk (Box 104, Folder 1525)
    Unlabeled disk.
  - Supreme People's Court Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 2001 February 9-23 (Box 104, Folder 1526)
    Washington, DC, New Orleans, San Francisco, and Los Angeles.
  - Supreme People's Court Delegation - Report, Itinerary, and Thank Yous, 2001 February 9-23 (Box 104, Folder 1527)
  - Natural Disaster Preparedness, Response, and Community Involvement Delegation - Brochure, Namelists, Itinerary, and Background, 2001 March 24-April 6 (Box 104, Folder 1528)
    Visit sponsored by the U. S. Department of State.
  - Natural Disaster Preparedness, Response, and Community Involvement Delegation - Brochure, Namelists, Itinerary, and Background, 2001 March 24-April 6; FA772:067; Still Image (Box 147, Folder 1528)
    Snapshot of delegates
  - Natural Disaster Preparedness, Response, and Community Involvement Delegation - China (PRC), 2001 March 24-April 6 (Box 104, Folder 1529)
  - Natural Disaster Preparedness, Response, and Community Involvement Delegation - Hong Kong, 2001 March 24-April 6 (Box 104, Folder 1530)
  - Natural Disaster Preparedness, Response, and Community Involvement Delegation - Taiwan, 2001 March 24-April 6 (Box 104, Folder 1531)
  - Natural Disaster Preparedness, Response, and Community Involvement Delegation - Faxes, 2001 March 24-April 6 (Box 105, Folder 1532)
  - Natural Disaster Preparedness, Response, and Community Involvement Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 2001 March 24-April 6 (Box 105, Folder 1533)
    Washington, DC, Florida, and California. File also includes hotel and transportation arrangments.
  - Community College Leadership Delegation - Background and Planning, 2001 April 1-15 (Box 105, Folder 1534)
    Visit sponsored by the US-China Education Foundation, as part of its Community Colleges in China Project.
  - Community College Leadership Delegation - Brochure, Namelist, Itinerary, 2001 April 1-15 (Box 105, Folder 1535)
    File also includes reports on Social Work and Community Colleges in China, and on Student Career Counseling in Taiwan.
  - Community College Leadership Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 2001 April 1-15 (Box 105, Folder 1536)
    New York, Chicago, Cedar Rapids, Tempe, San Francisco
  - Community College Leadership Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 2001 April 1-15; FA772:068; Still Image (Box 147, Folder 1536)
    15 snapshots of delegates on trip.
  - Community College Leadership Delegation - Follow-Up, 2001 April 1-15 (Box 105, Folder 1537)
    Includes program evaluations.
  - K-12 Principals Delegation - Brochure, Namelist, Itinerary, Background, and Planning, 2001 June 5-19 (Box 105, Folder 1538)
  - K-12 Principals Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 2001 June 5-19 (Box 105, Folder 1539)
    Washington, DC, New York, Phoenix, San Francisco.
  - K-12 Principals Delegation - Report and Thank Yous, 2001 June 5-19 (Box 105, Folder 1540)
  - Taiwan Labor Leaders Delegation - Background and Planning, 2001 July 21-August 3 (Box 105, Folder 1541)
  - Taiwan Labor Leaders Delegation - Brochure, Namelist, Itinerary, and Delegate Information, 2001 July 21-August 3 (Box 105, Folder 1542)
  - Taiwan Labor Leaders Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 2001 July 21-August 3 (Box 106, Folder 1543)
    Boston, Washington, DC, Detroit, and Seattle. Also includes hotel arrangements.
  - Taiwan Labor Leaders Delegation - Literature (Boston and Washington, DC), 2001 July 21-August 3 (Box 106, Folder 1544)
  - Taiwan Labor Leaders Delegation - Literature (Detroit and Seattle), 2001 July 21-August 3 (Box 106, Folder 1545)
  - Taiwan Labor Leaders Delegation - Reports, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 2001 July 21-August 3 (Box 106, Folder 1546)
  - K-12 Education Delegation, 2002 January 22-February 5 (Box 106, Folder 1547)
  - Court Specialization Delegation - Brochure, Namelist, Background, and Budget, 2002 March 2-14 (Box 106, Folder 1548)
  - Court Specialization Delegation - Correspondence, 2002 March 2-14 (Box 107, Folder 1549)
    Correspondence with China and with the American Consulate concerning the delegation and planning.
  - Court Specialization Delegation - Participants, 2002 March 2-14 (Box 107, Folder 1550)
  - Court Specialization Delegation - Visits and Meeting, 2002 March 2-14 (Box 107, Folder 1551)
    Washington, DC, Pittsburgh, Oklahoma City, San Francisco.
  - Court Specialization Delegation - Report, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 2002 March 2-14 (Box 107, Folder 1552)
  - University-Based Clinical Legal Aid Delegation - Brochure, Itinerary, Namelist, Budget, and Correspondence, 2002 April 6-17 (Box 107, Folder 1553)
  - University-Based Clinical Legal Aid Delegation - Background Materials, 2002 April 6-17 (Box 107, Folder 1554)
    Background information on clinical law. Materials in English and Chinese.
  - University-Based Clinical Legal Aid Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 2002 April 6-17 (Box 107, Folder 1555)
    Boston, New York, Washington, DC. Includes background information on legal aid organizations.
  - University-Based Clinical Legal Aid Delegation - Thank Yous, 2002 April 6-17 (Box 107, Folder 1556)
    There is no report in the file.
  - Shandong Provincial High People's Court Delegation, 2002 May 14-25 (Box 107, Folder 1557)
    The NCUSCR provided facilitative help for the delegation's visit.
  - Economic Development and Environmental Management, Hazardous Waste Study Tour - Brochure, Namelist, Background, and Planning, 2002 June 22-July 5 (Box 107, Folder 1558)
  - Economic Development and Environmental Management, Hazardous Waste Study Tour - Participants, 2002 June 22-July 5 (Box 107, Folder 1559)
  - Economic Development and Environmental Management, Hazardous Waste Study Tour - Visits and Meetings, 2002 June 22-July 5 (Box 107, Folder 1560)
    Washington, DC, Houston, and New Orleans. Includes material on hotels and transportation.
  - Economic Development and Environmental Management, Hazardous Waste Study Tour - Reports, Itinerary, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 2002 June 22-July 5 (Box 107, Folder 1561)
  - Jiangsu Culture and Friendship Delegation, 2002 June 23-July 1 (Box 107, Folder 1562)
    Also known as the Jiangsu Cultural Industry Delegation. The National Committee arranged meetings in New York for the delegation on June 25.
  - K-12 English Teachers Delegation - Brochure, Namelist, Background, and Planning, 2002 July 27-August 10 (Box 108, Folder 1563)
  - K-12 English Teachers Delegation - Visits, Meetings, and Follow-Up, 2002 July 27-August 10 (Box 108, Folder 1564)
    Boston, Washington, DC, Montana, and San Francisco. File includes material on hotels and transportation.
  - K-12 English Teachers Delegation - Visits, Meetings, and Follow-Up, 2002 July 27-August 10; FA772:069; Still Image (Box 147, Folder 1564)
    105 shapshots of delegation trip.
  - Special Education Delegation - Brochure, Namelist, Itinerary, Background, and Planning, 2002 October 16-30 (Box 108, Folder 1565)
  - Special Education Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 2002 October 16-30 (Box 108, Folder 1566)
    Boston, Washington, DC, Minnesota, San Francisco
  - Special Education Delegation - Thank Yous and Follow-Up, 2002 October 16-30 (Box 108, Folder 1567)
  - Special Education Delegation - Thank Yous and Follow-Up, 2002 October 16-30; FA772:070; Still Image (Box 147, Folder 1567)
    Approximately 80 snapshots of delegation trip.
  - Election Observation Delegation - Brochure, Namelists, Itinerary, Reports, Background, and Planning, 2002 October 30-November 10 (Box 108, Folder 1568)
    Also known as Elections in the United States and Greater China Delegation.
  - Election Observation Delegation - Correspondence, 2002 October 30-November 10 (Box 108, Folder 1569)
  - Election Observation Delegation - Participant Bios, 2002 October 30-November 10 (Box 108, Folder 1570)
  - Election Observation Delegation - Notes, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 2002 October 30-November 10 (Box 108, Folder 1571)
    Notes consist of manuscript notes on program presentations and discussions, presumably recorded by Margot Landman.
  - HIV - AIDS Education and Outreach Fellows - Brochure, Itinerary, and Planning, 2003 June 28-August 23 (Box 108, Folder 1572)
    Study Tour, June 28 - July 7; Fellow Placements, July 8 - August 23. Includes some participant and program information. Materials concerning housing and travel added to this file.
  - HIV - AIDS Education and Outreach Fellows - Participants, 2003 June 28-August 23 (Box 108, Folder 1573)
    Study Tour, June 28 - July 7; Fellow Placements, July 8 - August 23. File includes unidentified photo of delegates (?) outside a New York restaurant (photo not separated from file).
  - HIV - AIDS Education and Outreach Fellows - Host Institutions and Contacts, 2003 June 28-August 23 (Box 108, Folder 1574)
    Study Tour, June 28 - July 7; Fellow Placements, July 8 - August 23.
  - HIV - AIDS Education and Outreach Fellows - San Francisco Wrap-Up, 2003 June 28-August 23 (Box 108, Folder 1575)
    The participants met in San Francisco from August 20-23.
  - HIV - AIDS Education and Outreach Fellows - Follow-Up, 2003 June 28-August 23 (Box 109, Folder 1576)
    Subsequent proposals to the U. S. Department of State, for projects on "Developing Effective Media Campaigns for HIV/AIDS Education in China" and " Community Planning for HIV/AIDS Prevention and Treatment in China" added to this file.
  - Anti-Corruption Delegation, 2003 September 13-27 (Box 109, Folder 1577)
    From China's Ministry of Supervision.
  - Shandong Provincial High People's Court Delegation, 2003 September 16-26 (Box 109, Folder 1578)
    The NCUSCR provided facilitative help for the judges' visit.
  - K-12 Education Delegation - Itinerary, Namelist, and Planning, 2003 September 26-October 16 (Box 109, Folder 1579)
    Also described as English Teachers delegation.
  - K-12 Education Delegation - Visits and Meetings, 2003 September 26-October 16 (Box 109, Folder 1580)
    Also described as English Teachers delegation. Boston, Philadelphia, Washington, Atlanta, Oklahoma, and San Francisco. File contains correspondence with escort Lawrence Daks concerning itinerary and visit planning.
  - K-12 Education Delegation - Report, Evaluations, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 2003 September 26-October 16 (Box 109, Folder 1581)
  - K-12 Education Delegation - Report, Evaluations, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 2003 September 26-October 16; FA772:071; Still Image (Box 147, Folder 1581)
    Group photo and snapshots of delegation trip
  - Hi-Tech Application in Agricultural Production Delegation, 2004 January 6-8 (Box 109, Folder 1582)
    The NCUSCR organized the delegation's New York visit.
  - Worker Displacement Policy Fellows - General, 2004 March 11-April 10 (Box 109, Folder 1583)
    Includes Planning, Host Institutions and Advisors, and Logistics.